# UDEH, OLUCHUKWU PRECIOUS

### 08106377275, udeh.oluchukwu@gmail.com

(Department of Human Kinetics and Health Education, University of Nigeria, Nsukka, Enugu State)

Personal Statement:

I'm an excellent project manager, I have a unique experience with dealing with people from different backgrounds, working under pressure and a sincere willingness to learn, improve and contribute immense value to any team I work with. I am focused, resilient and dedicated.

Nationality:

Nigerian

Educational Institutions /
Academic Qualifications obtained with Dates.

- University of Nigeria, Nsukka; Master of Science in Psychology of Sports(In-view).
- University of Nigeria, Nsukka, 2013-2017; Bachelor of Science in Physical Education and Recreation, First Class Honours (CGPA, 4.82).
- Carol Standard Convent, Ichi, Anambra State, 2007- 2013; West African Senior School Certificate Examination, (WASSCE).

Professional Certification /Additional Trainings.

- Certificate of Registration, TRCN, 2017.
- Currently undergoing a web development training with ZuriNG
- Currently enrolled into a programme on Emotional Intelligence with LinkedIn.
- A student of Public Service and Governance with the Africa for Africa School of Government.
- Certificate of Achievement, by MISK Global Forum and FullBridge on completion of MGF Future Fit (Professional Development) Program.
- Certificate of Completion, Front-End Fundamentals via Pirple.com
- Successfully completed a MOOC on Introduction to Project Management on edx.org.

**Working Experiences** 

**Assistant Manager, Operations** at Udek-h Prints Ltd, Anambra State. **Sept.2019 – February, 2021**.

#### Key responsibilities:

Task Scheduling and delegation

- Coordination of Project meeting reviews
- Project reporting to the executive office/ MD
- Documentation of client briefs and proposals
- Vendor management and reporting to the executive office

Administrative Staff / Secretary- Alumni Relations Unit, Emmanuel Alayande College of Education, Oyo, Oyo State, (National Youth Service), Sept, 2018 – June, 2019.

### Key Responsibilities:

 Collecting, Collating and sorting of alumni data; minutes taking and documentation.

Volunteer Assistant at Loveworld Youth Resource Centre, Sept. 2017 - July, 2019.

## Key Responsibilities:

- Organisation of seminars and trainings for students;
- Monitoring and reporting the activities organised to the director.

Volunteer Student Teacher at St. Teresa's College, Nsukka. 2016

Volunteer Student Teacher at Hillview Unique Sec. School, Nsukka, 2015

#### Awards/ Recognition with Dates:

- Certificate of Acknowledgement, as NYSC Sustainable Development Goals Advocate, 2018/2019.
- Certificate of Merit, Best Graduating Student of the Faculty of Education, 2016/2017.

Certificate of Good service as Clerk, House of Representatives, Faculty of Education Students' Association, University of Nigeria, Nsukka, 2017.

### Skills and Abilities:

- Proficiency in Basic Computer Usage (Microsoft Word & Excel) including basic computer programming (Front-End Web Development)
- Exceptional organization, record-keeping and management Skills
- Excellent interpersonal and customer service skills.
- Effective communication, interactive and problem-solving skills
- Good leadership and collaboration skills

- Attention to details
- Competent in worksite health safety &first siding
- Quick learner and active listener..

Extra-Curricular Activities (Hobbies):

Researching and Reading

Names and Addresses of Referees:

Names and addresses of referees will be provided if required.